Guide to the Behind the Veil: Documenting African-American Life in the Jim Crow South Records, 1940-1997 and undated, bulk 1993-1997 RL.00170
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 2009-0012, 13 items
  - Turrentine, Coy, 51
    - Original audiocassette, 1995 May 30 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-050)
      Interview with Pastor Coy Turrentine, conducted by Obadiah Manley in Pasadena, California
    - Releases, 1995 May (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - History 161 class papers and documents, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Accession 2013-0108
  - A Compilation of Interviews, 1994; 2 disks (Box Acc. 13/108: Box 1)
    Two DVDs (RL.00170-DVD-001 copies 1 and 2) of 33 .mp3 files from Behind the Veil interviews conducted in 1994.
- Audio recordings - associated interview cassettes, 1991-1997; 1; 90 items
  This series includes audiocassettes associated with other recordings in the collection. Some may contain unique interview material.
  - Barnes, Lenzie, 1
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October 23 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-031)
      Interview with Lenzie Barnes, conducted by Ben Glenn
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 November 25 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-032)
  - Bowles, Pauline, 2
    - Original audiocassette, 1998 July 23 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-061)
      Interview with Mrs. Pauline Bowles in Gainesville, Florida
  - Boyd, Ruth Spalding, 3
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October 22 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-033)
      Interview with Ruth Spalding Boyd, conducted by Serena Rhodie in Durham, North Carolina
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October 22 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-034)
  - Braswell, Martha, 4
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-001)
      Interview with Martha Braswell, conducted by Janet Reilly
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-002)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-003)
  - Bryant, R. Kelly, 8
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October 28 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-035)
      Interview with R. Kelly Bryant, conducted by Jennifer Steen
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 November 15 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-036)
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-078)
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-079)
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 November 15 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-080)
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 November 15 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-081)
  - Canty, Mary, 9
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-062)
      Interview with Mary Canty in Fort Marie/Memphis, Tennassee
  - Chatmon, Thomas, 10
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-063)
      Interview with Thomas Chatmon
  - Cousin, Rev. Phillip R., 11
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-037)
      Interview with Rev. Phillip R. Cousin, conducted by Kim Deiml
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 November 06 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-038)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-082)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-083)
  - Cross, Blondale, 12
    - Original audiocassette, 1995 June 23 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-094)
      Interview with Blondale Cross, conducted by Paul Ortiz in Memphis, Tennessee
  - Davis, Julius, 13
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-039)
      Interview with Julius Davis, conducted by Eric Johnson in Durham, North Carolina
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-040)
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-041)
  - DeLaine, Marguirite, 14
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-064)
      Interview with Marguirite DeLaine
  - Giles, Alice, 16
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-067)
      Interview with Alice Giles
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-068)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-086)
  - Goodwin, Margaret S., 17
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-004)
      Interview with Margaret S. Goodwin, conducted by Kristen Lee
    - Original audiocassette, 1997 April 12 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-005)
  - Hall, James, 18
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-069)
      Interview with James Hall
  - Johnson, Georgie, 21
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-006)
      Interview with Georgie Johnson, conducted by Keisha Roberts
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-007)
  - Jones, Dorothy, 22
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-008)
      Interview with Dorothy Jones, conducted by Kristen Koeker
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-009)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-010)
  - Jones, Elaine, 23
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-011)
      Interview with Elaine Jones, conducted by Amy Murnick
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-012)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-013)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-014)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-015)
  - Lyons, Bettie, 24
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-016)
      Interview with Bettie Lyons, conducted by Mi Young Ryee
  - Mabry, Corine, 25
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-017)
      Interview with Corine Mabry, conducted by Abrielle Beaton
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-018)
  - Manasse, Ernst, 26
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 April 06 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-109)
      Interview with Ernst Manasse, conducted by Kellie Kenyota Daniels, Behind the Veil undergraduate class, Durham, North Carolina
  - Mason, Earnest, 27
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 April 12 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-127)
      Interview with Earnest Mason
  - Mosley, Daisy Mae Livingson, 28
    - Original audiocassette, 1993 December 18 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-054)
      Interview with Daisy Mae Livingston Mosley, conducted by Michelle Harris and James Anderson
  - Nelson, Margaret, 29
    - Original audiocassette, 1995 July 05 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-055)
      Interview with Margaret Nelson, conducted by Mary Hebert
    - Original audiocassette, 1995 July 05 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-056)
  - Nixon, Cornelius E., Jr., 30
    - Original audiocassette, 1993 July 19 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-058)
      Interview with Cornelius E. Nixon, Jr., conducted by Karen Ferguson
    - Original audiocassette, 1993 July 19 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-057)
      Interview with Cornelius E. Nixon, Jr., conducted by Karen Ferguson in Wilmington, North Carolina
  - Osborne, Ruby, 31
    - Original audiocassette, 1997 November 02 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-019)
      Interview with Ruby Osborn, conducted by Andrea Smith
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-020)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-084)
    - Original audiocassette, 1997 November 02 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-085)
  - Page, Mildred, 32
    - Original audiocassette, 1995 June 01 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-051)
      Interview with Mildred Page, conducted by F. Woods and D. Dixon
  - Parker, Creola, 33
    - Original audiocassette, 1997 October 20 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-021)
      Interview with Creola Parker, conducted by Serena Rhodie
  - Parker, Florida, 34
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-052)
      Interview with Florida Parker, conducted by Tywanna Whorley
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-053)
  - Patterson, Annie, 35
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-022)
      Interview with Annie Patterson, conducted by Sara Forgione
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-023)
  - Pinderhughes, James, 36
    - Original audiocassette, 2004 June 06 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-155)
      Interview with James Pinderhughes, conducted by Rhonda Jones
    - Original audiocassette, 2004 June 06 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-156)
  - Pointer, Ann S., 37
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 July 22 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-070)
      Interview with Ann S. Pointer, conducted by Paul Ortiz
  - RH tobacco worker, 38
    - Original audiocassette, Undated (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-128)
      Interview with an RH tobacco worker, conducted by Rick McKnight
  - Rivera, Alex, 39
    - Original audiocassette, 1995 June 02 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-059)
      Interview with Alex Rivera, conducted by F. Woods and M. Hebert
    - Original audiocassette, 1995 June 02 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-060)
  - Rose, Richard, 40
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-071)
      Interview with Richard Rose
  - Roundtree, Gwen, 41
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-024)
      Interview with Gwen Roundtree, conducted by Mi Young Ryee
  - Shaw, Catherine, 42
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-025)
      Interview with Catherine Shaw, conducted by Carmen Alexander
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-026)
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-027)
  - Shaw, Hollis, 43
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-028)
      Interview with Hollis Shaw, conducted by Peter Messick
    - Original audiocassette, 1997 November 14 (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-029)
  - Sims, Constant; Sims, Constant and Forrest, E., 44
    - Original audiocassette, 1995 June 19 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-106)
      Interview with Constant Sims and interview with Constant Sims and E. Forrest, conducted by S. Scales
  - Small, Henry, 45
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 August 14 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-072)
      Interview with Henry Small, conducted by Tunga White and Sally Graham
  - Smith, Mary Hester, 46
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October 28 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-042)
      Interview with Mary Hester Smith, conducted by Nicole Spira in Durham, North Carolina
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October 28 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-043)
  - Speight, Theodore, 47
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 1, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-030)
      Interview with Theodore Speight interview, conducted by Will Wiseman
  - Sutton, Virginia, 49
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-073)
      Interview with Virginia Sutton
  - Thorpe, Amelia, 50
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-044)
      Interview with Amelia Thorpe, conducted by Julie Zwibelman in Durham, North Carolina
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-045)
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 November 11 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-046)
  - White, Nathaniel, Sr., 52
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October 14 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-047)
      Interview with Nathaniel White, Sr., conducted by Robert Carroll in Durham, North Carolina at 1:10 pm
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 October 14 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-048)
    - Original audiocassette, 1996 November 11 (Box 2, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-049)
  - Williams, Curtis, 53
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-074)
      Interview with Curtis Williams
  - Williams, Henry and Ellis, Orian, 54
    - Original audiocassette, 1998 July 28 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-075)
      Interview with Henry Williams and Orian Ellis in Gainesville, Florida
    - Original audiocassette, 1998 July 28 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-076)
  - Wright, Jessie, 55
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 July 20 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-077)
      Interview with Jessie Wright, conducted by Paul Ortiz in Tuskegee, Alabama
- Audio recordings - associated administrative cassettes, 1991-1997; 2; 54 items
  This series contains audiocassette recordings associated with the administration of the project and with related seminars and workshops.
  - Behind the Veil Research Team: Oral History with Bill Chafe, 56
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 June 02 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-088)
      Behind the Veil Research Team: Oral History with Bill Chaffe
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 June 02 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-089)
  - Behind the Veil: African American Life in the Jim Crow South Meeting, 57
    - Original audiocassette, 1999 October 26 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-097)
      Behind the Veil Meeting
    - Original audiocassette, 1999 November 09 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-098)
  - Behind the Veil: African American Life in the Jim Crow South Meeting, 58
    - Original audiocassette, 1999 November 30 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-101)
      Behind the Veil Meeting: Discussion on new press text/book
  - Behind the Veil: African American Life in the Jim Crow South Research Conference, 59
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 March 16 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-142)
      Behind the Veil: African American Life in the Jim Crow South Research Conference, Session 2; Economics: 'African American Life: Economic Contexts' with Mann Woodruff, Gavin Wright, and Joe Trotter
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 March 16 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-143)
      Behind the Veil: African American Life in the Jim Crow South Research Conference, Session 3: 'Expressive Culture' with Richard Powell
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 March 17 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-144)
      Behind the Veil: African American Life in the Jim Crow South Research Conference, Session 4: 'Autonomous Institutions' with Evelyn Brooks Higginbottam and Walter B. Wearne
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 March 16 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-141)
      Behind the Veil: African American Life in the Jim Crow South Research Conference, Session I; Political: 'Political Realities of Jim Crow' with Elsa Barkley Brown and Robin D.G. Kelly
  - Behind the Veil: African American Life in the Jim Crow South Seminar, 60
    - Original audiocassette, 1999 November 16 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-100)
      Behind the Veil Seminar
    - Original audiocassette, 1999 October 19 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-107)
  - Behind the Veil: African American Life in the Jim Crow South Undergraduate Class, 61
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 March 17 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-103)
      Behind the Veil Undergraduate class, guest Dr. Helen G. Edmonds
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 March 17 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-104)
  - Behind the Veil: West End Oral History of Durham, NC, 62
    - Original audiocassette, 1993 November 20 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-090)
      West End Oral History Project of Durham, NC interview, conducted by Paul Ortiz
    - Original audiocassette, 1993 November 20 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-091)
  - Brown, William, 63
    - Original audiocassette, 1995 June 09 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-087)
      Interview with William Brown, conducted by Obadiah Manley in Pasadena, California
  - Charlotte Meeting, 64
    - Original audiocassette, 1993 May 19 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-102)
      Charlotte Meeting, with Vermelle Ely, Price Davis, Ruby McCathorine, Brunn, and Valk
  - Crossing the Color Line, 65
    - Original audiocassette, 1993 May 13 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-108)
      Crossing the Color Line - Shadows-on-the-Teche, New Iberia, Louisiana: Interviews/discussions regarding integration/desegregation in schools
  - Enfield Meeting, 66
    - Original audiocassette, 1993 May 14 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-096)
      Enfield Meeting with Margaret ---, Colin Carnegey, Minnie White, Mrs. Willis, Brann, Vaul, and Stewart
  - JCP Summer Institute, 67
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 04 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-130)
      Beverly Jones and Bob Korstad Presentations: Industrial Workers, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 04 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-131)
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 19 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-119)
      Charles Frye Presentation: Everyday Culture, JCP Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 19 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-120)
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 15 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-123)
      Charles Reagan Wilson Presentation: The Multicultural South, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 15 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-124)
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 15 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-136)
      Christina Greene Practicum: Curriculum Development; JCP Curriculum Development Project discussion, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 09 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-118)
      Evelyn Brooks Higgenbottom Presentation: The Black Church During the Jim Crow Era, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 09 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-121)
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 11 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-110)
      Gavin Wright Presentation: Economics of Segregation, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 11 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-111)
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 03 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-135)
      Ginny Daley Practicum, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 18 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-126)
      Glenn Hinson Presentation: Venacular Voices in Folklore and Folklife, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 09 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-140)
      Iris Hill and Bob Hall Practicum: Publishing Documentary Work, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 23 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-113)
      Jacqueline A. Rouse Presentation: Lugenia Burns Hope Women's Voluntary Associations, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 10 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-116)
      James Anderson Presentation: Education, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 10 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-117)
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 22 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-122)
      Karen Fields Presentation: Life in the Low Country 'Things Done Regardles, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 22 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-125)
      Karen Fields Presentation: Things Done Regardless, and Practicum: Oral History Methodology, both at JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 02 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-112)
      Lynn Marshall Linnemeier Presentation, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 05 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-134)
      Pete Daniel Practicum: Material Culture Museums, continued with James Eatin, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 05 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-133)
      Pete Daniel Practicum: Material Culture Museums, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 05 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-132)
      Pete Daniel Presentation: Southern Agriculture, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 11 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-138)
      Robert Byrd Practicum: Archives, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 12 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-114)
      Robin D.G. Kelly Presentation:Everyday Forms of Resisting, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 12 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-115)
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 08 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-129)
      Tera Hunter Presentation: Women and Work, JCP Summer Institute
    - Original audiocassette, 1991 July 12 (Box 4, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-139)
      Valeria Lee Practicum: Fundraising, JCP Summer Institute
  - Meeting, 68
    - Original audiocassette, Undated (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-154)
      Meeting
  - New Bern Meeting, 69
    - Original audiocassette, 1993 May 06; 1993 May 07 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-095)
      New Bern Meetings including Memories of New Bern Community Chair Joe Patterson and Meeting with Grace George, Mary White, and Francis Jones
  - Rosewood Reborn, 70
    - Original audiocassette, 1997 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-092)
      Rosewood Reborn
    - Original audiocassette, 1997 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-093)
  - Tillery Community Center Open Minded Seniors, 71
    - Original audiocassette, 1994 June 24 (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-105)
      Tillery Community Center Open Minded Seniors group interview
    - Original audiocassette, undated (Box 3, Audio-cassette RL00170-CS-099)
      Tillery Community Center Open Minded Seniors Health Award Symposium
- Electronic records - associated diskettes, 1991-1997; 1; 761 items
  Series includes 761 disks, including 3.5" floppy disks, zip disks, and one optical disc, associated with the Behind the Veil project and containing transcript and administrative material.
  - Disks, 1 (Box 7, Box 8)
    - Aaron, Delores - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0001)
    - Alexander, Leon - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0002)
    - Alexander, Leon - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0003)
    - Allen, Johnny and Ida - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0004)
    - Andrews, Malachia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0005)
    - Andrews, Malachia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0006)
    - Archie, Johnnie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0007)
    - Attmore, Arlestus - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0008)
    - Auguster, Edran - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0009)
    - Bethune, Thelma - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0010)
    - Bijou, Hattie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0011)
    - Blaise, Edward - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0012)
    - Borders, Florence - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0013)
    - Boucree, John H. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0014)
    - Bouise, Louise M. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0015)
    - Bowie, Eura - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0016)
    - Flemming, Cora - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0016)
    - Boyd, Leroy 1983 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0017)
    - Boyd, Leroy - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0018)
    - Branch, Lanetha J. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0019)
    - Brown, Earl - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0020)
    - Browne, Corrine - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0021)
    - Bryant, Artelia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0022)
    - Bryant, Eddie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0023)
    - Butler, Willie P. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0024)